<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Mobile Treasure Hunt</string>

    <string name="start">Start Treasure Hunt</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="next_clue">Next Clue</string>
    <string name="quit">QUIT</string>
    <string name="found_it">FOUND IT!</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="rules">RULES</string>

    <string name="clue_1">Clue #1</string>
    <string name="clue_1_info">More Information Regarding Clue #1</string>
    <string name="clue_1_description">This scene was filmed at Hector\'s Garage at 401 El Segundo Blvd, El Segundo, CA. Brian O\'Connor sneaked into Hector\'s garage for reconnaissance of stolen equipments. O\'Connor was accused of being a cop, but he slyly escaped after lying that he sneaked in to gain an advantage for the upcoming Race Wars.</string>
    <string name="hint_clue_1">Reveal Hint for Clue #1</string>
    <string name="hint_description">This is one of the legendary memes from The Fast and the Furious Movie. This hint points to the location of the \'He\'s a Cop!\' scene where Brian O\'Conner tries to escape alive while being interrogated by Toretto and Vince. See image.</string>

    <string name="clue_2">Clue #2</string>
    <string name="clue_2_info">More Information Regarding Clue #2</string>
    <string name="clue_2_description">The race itself (where Paul loses his car) was held on Prairie Avenue in the city of Hawthorne, a good 15 miles southwest of the Produce Market. The street runs north and south, past the western edge of the Hawthorne Airport. They were racing north on Prairie, starting at Prairie and 120th Street, and finishing at Prairie and 118th Street (just south of the 105 Freeway).They also filmed some of the pre &amp; post race scenes south of 120th. \n\nReference: (https://www.seeing-stars.com/Locations/FastAndFurious.shtml)</string>
    <string name="hint_clue_2">Reveal Hint for Clue #2</string>
    <string name="hint_description2">When Brian O\'Conner lost his 10-second car to Toretto in their first race together, O\'Conner said he \'almost had him\' referring that he almost beat Toretto, a racing legend. Toretto put O\'Conner in his place with this iconic quote. This hint points to the location where this quote was spoken.</string>

    <string name="clue_3">Clue #3</string>
    <string name="clue_3_details">This scene was filmed at the famous Dodgers Stadium at 1000 Vin Scully Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90012. The parking lot was the location where Brian O\'Conner was testing out his new 10-second car.</string>
    <string name="clue_3_info">More Information Regarding Clue #3</string>
    <string name="clue_3_description">In the opening scene of The Fast and the Furious, viewers are introduced to the main character, Brian O\'Conner and his famous green Mitsubishi Eclipse. O\'Conner was testing out his Eclipse at this location. Can you guess this location?</string>
    <string name="hint_clue_3">Reveal Hint for Clue #3</string>

    <string name="clue_4">Clue #4</string>
    <string name="clue_4_details">Walter White Jr. (the son) made a fundraiser website for his dad, Walter White, because he has cancer and he needed to afford the cost of healthcare. The website was shown on Breaking Bad, and the interesting thing is that it actually exists in real life. You can visit at: http://www.savewalterwhite.com/. Their home was located at 308 Negra Arroyo Lane, Albuquerque, New Mexico 87104.</string>
    <string name="clue_4_info">More Information Regarding Clue #4</string>
    <string name="clue_4_description">In Breaking Bad, Walter White (in image) has cancer and his son created a website to support his dad\'s cancer treatment. Where was this scene taken place?</string>
    <string name="hint_clue_4">Reveal Hint for Clue #4</string>

    <string name="clue_5">Clue #5</string>
    <string name="clue_5_details">This scene was filmed at North Cove Marina, 385 South End Avenue near the World Financial Center in New York City. The yacht Jordan Belford was on is called Naomi.</string>
    <string name="clue_5_info">More Information Regarding Clue #5</string>
    <string name="clue_5_description">Before Jordan Belford (pictured) leaves New York for Europe, he got a visit from the FBI agent because Belford was under suspicion that he was operating his firm illegally. Belford tried to bribe the agent, which was unsuccessful and led to a short, passive-aggressive meeting. Can you find the location where this scene was filmed at?</string>
    <string name="hint_clue_5">Reveal Hint for Clue #5</string>

    <string name="clue_6">Clue #6</string>
    <string name="clue_6_details">Even though the movie takes place in San Francisco and Alcatraz, some of the scenes were actually shot at Los Angeles. The hotel that John Mason was getting his haircut is located at Millennium Biltmore Hotel Los Angeles. Address: 506 S Grand Ave, Los Angeles, CA 90071</string>
    <string name="clue_6_info">More Information Regarding Clue #6</string>
    <string name="clue_6_description">In the movie, \'The Rock\', Stanley Goodspeed (FBI Agent) monitors the barber and a prisoner, John Mason, as Mason is getting a haircut. Shortly after, Mason threw the police chief off the balcony with a string of rope attached to the police chief\'s wrist and tied the other endpoint of the rope to a chair. The police chief is left dangling from this tall building. Mason then made his attempt to escape. Where was this filmed at?</string>
    <string name="hint_clue_6">Reveal Hint for Clue #6</string>

    <string name="clue_7">Clue #7</string>
    <string name="clue_7_details">Peter Parker is a nerd and is often depended on by others that need help academically. Socially, people avoid Parker and sometimes bullies him. Parker was suffering low self-esteem after being taken advantaged of and Parker accidentally got in contact with a symbiote. The symbiote helped Parker by boosting his mentality and overcome the nice guy syndrome until things turn to worse for Parker and his close relationship with MJ, Harry Osborn, and his Aunt May.</string>
    <string name="clue_7_info">More Information Regarding Clue #7</string>
    <string name="clue_7_description">In Spider-man 3, Peter Parker has already been consumed by a symbiote that makes him overly confident, arrogant, and fearless. He went into his usual job that he held for more than 3 years, and is often underpaid and not respected by his boss, Jonah Jameson Jr. One day, Parker got sick of the lowball offer and fired back at Jameson with this legendary quote that fulfilled Parker\'s request. Where is the real life location of this building?</string>
    <string name="hint_clue_7">Reveal Hint for Clue #7</string>

    <string name="clue_8">Clue #8</string>
    <string name="clue_8_details">Flipper is an actual dolphin that is also a mascot for Miami Dolphins. Flipper went missing and Ace Ventura was called in to investigate. The investigation led to hilarious pursuit of the truth and guaranteed to make some people\'s cheek hurt from laughing. This scene was taken place at Hard Rock Stadium in Miami. </string>
    <string name="clue_8_info">More Information Regarding Clue #8</string>
    <string name="clue_8_description">In \'Ace Ventura: Pet Detective\', Ace was called in by a professional football team to investigate the disappearance of Flipper, their living mascot dolphin. Ace was investigating Flipper\'s pool for clues. Where is this football stadium located? </string>
    <string name="hint_clue_8">Reveal Hint for Clue #8</string>

    <string name="clue_9">Clue #9</string>
    <string name="clue_9_details">This house was filmed at 3547 Combahee Rd, Yemassee, South Carolina. This famous home is no longer around as it got demolished right after the filming of the movie due to not up to code.</string>
    <string name="clue_9_info">More Information Regarding Clue #9</string>
    <string name="clue_9_description">The house where this family lived in.</string>
    <string name="hint_clue_9">Reveal Hint for Clue #9</string>

    <string name="clue_10">Clue #10</string>
    <string name="clue_10_details">This parody was filmed in Austin Powers in Goldmember which was taken place at Moab, Utah.</string>
    <string name="clue_10_info">More Information Regarding Clue #10</string>
    <string name="clue_10_description">In \'Austin Powers in Goldmember\', Tom Cruise is acting as Austin Powers for a parody movie directed by the real Austin Powers. Austin Powers (Tom Cruise) flips over an attack chopper and destroys the enemy and escaped unscathed. Austin Power (Tom Cruise) is then introduced by Dixie Normous who is played by Gwyneth Paltrow. Where was this stunt filmed at?</string>
    <string name="hint_clue_10">Reveal Hint for Clue #10</string>

    <string name="clue_info">Information</string>

    <string name="permission">App Permission</string>















    <string name="walter_white">An image of Walter White for a Fundraiser</string>
    <string name="connor_quote">Quote from the legendary Fast and the Furious movie</string>
    <string name="dodgers_stadium">A picture of a famous Green Mitsubishi Eclipse that Brian O\'Conner drove at the opening scene of The Fast and The Furious.</string>

</resources>